<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:g-custom="http://base.google.com/cns/1.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>comcatdigital</title>
    <link>http://www.comcat.co.za</link>
    <description />
    <atom:link href="http://www.comcat.co.za/feed/rss2" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self" />
    <item>
      <title>Reboot your business</title>
      <link>http://www.comcat.co.za/reboot-your-business</link>
      <description>Time to reboot your business. Go DIGITAL. Improve sales and lower ad costs.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 style="transition: opacity 1s ease-in-out 0s;"&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         Go Digital
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/md/unsplash/dms3rep/multi/photo-1537606845186-9921373c310f.jpg"/&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div style="transition: none 0s ease 0s; display: block;" data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;span style="background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           When you started the year, you never realised that 2020 will be the year of lockdown. Being a business owner, this has been a stressful time. How to maintain an income? How to pay rent? How to pay employees? Will the clients remain loyal and come back to support my business? These are all questions that keep small business owners awake at night. 
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;span style="background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);"&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Some small businesses have stayed their course and are now in need of rescue or has been forced to close their doors.  Many entrepreneurs have seen lockdown as an opportunity and changed the way they do business. This has been beneficial to them because they are now thriving and is better off. 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          They realised that it is less likely that the clients will come to them, so they decided to go to the clients. After some research was done, they noticed that internet and social media usage increase exponentially. Therefore, going digital was key. They could reach their current and potential clients while decreasing the risk of exposure to C19.
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          So how did they do it?
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Going digital can be like walking on a mine field. Don’t just jump in and think that you will get clients in the first try. In the beginning there will be more misses than hits. This is when having the right strategy is key. These are just some of the guidelines to help you transfer to digital.
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;h3 style=""&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         1.	Setup high converting website or ecommerce site
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;span style="background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           Having an old outdated website is like going to a job interview with a pair of flip-flops, shorts and t-shirt. It does not leave a good impression and you are less likely to get the job. The same is for websites. If your competitors have a sleek, modern looking website that is optimised for mobile, pc and tablet, people are more likely to go with them. 
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Having an ecommerce site makes it easier to browse your products without physically going to your store. Integrate ecommerce store with a payment portal and your clients can now purchase your products and services from the convenience of their homes. All payment platforms charge a small service fee, but most of them are still cheaper than the in store pay point card readers. This in turn decreased the chances of spreading the virus.
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;h3&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         2.	Get to know your top clients
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;a&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/md/unsplash/dms3rep/multi/photo-1556742049-0cfed4f6a45d.jpg" alt=""/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;span style="background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           For me personally this is one of the most important topics. How well do you know your top clients? Do you know why they shop with you and what makes them come back? If you don’t know this, how to you expect to get more high quality returning clients?  Next time you see your clients, have a chat about their interest, habits and hobbies. Make notes and this will help you reach new potential clients. 
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          For example: A mother drops off her kids at school in the morning. On her way home she pops in at your shop to make a purchase. With this information, you can already start to target new potential clients in a 5 – 10km radius of your shop. Use the demographics to narrow down your target audience.  This will help you increase conversion while keeping your cost low.
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;h3&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         3.	Create a jaw dropping special or free guide 
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;span style="background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           Having an offer that is of value will help you attract more clients. This can either be something for free or a jaw dropping offer but needs to provide value to your clients.  After you have created your list of top clients, an offer can be catered for your avatar(s). This increases your conversion and return on ad spent.
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Example: Provide a free diet plan or an offer of first month free when taking a 12-month contract. You still provide value to your clients and this is the building blocks of starting a relationship with your clients.
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;h3&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         4.	Create your sales funnel
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;a&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/conversion-funnel-5444126_1920.jpg" alt=""/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;span style="background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           What is a sales funnel? This is where you take your leads to all the steps to get a sale. Depending on your offer and how well your funnel is designed, will determine your conversion percentage. 
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Now a decision needs to be made on how you are going to approach your potential clients. You already have setup your offer, now to implement. 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Example: In the first step of sales funnel, offer your potential clients a free guide. Free is always the best seller. Here your lead to insert their details to get the guide and to opt in to newsletters or offers. When the details are entered, the lead is diverted to a thank-you page. Her you thank your client for showing interest in your free guide. This is now the perfect place to upsell another product. Create urgency like limited time/amount available.   
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          (Buy now and get 50% off before countdown expires. OR  Sign up for a year and get the first month on us. Limited spots available). 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Here is where most people say “We do not give anything for FREE!!” Have a look at this example
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          You have a service plan that you provide at $50 a month. Your offer is “sign up for a year and get the first month on us” You will now make $550 in the first year. If the client is happy with your service, you are looking to having the client for about 4 years. This makes the lifetime value of this client $2350. So at the end of the day, you have $2350 in your business while giving something away for free.
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;h3&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         5.	Decide on your platform
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;span style="background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           Choosing your platform depends on what your goal is. Social media is used to target a cold audience and your funnel needs to be designed accordingly. Using search engines, people are looking for your products and services so they are warm audiences and your funnel needs to be adjusted to accommodate this. Using social media is much cheaper than search engines.  Combine that with a funnel designed for an unaware audience, you should get a high return on ad-spent.
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;h3&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         6.	Setup ad
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;span style="background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           You should now have the following
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          •	Client’s demographics
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          •	Offer 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          •	Link to funnel
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          •	Decided on platform
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Now you have everything needed to run your campaign. All platforms are different so I am not going to deep dive into setting up an ad. If all the information has been gathered, then you have everything you need to start a campaign.
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;h3&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         7.	Follow up
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;span style="background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           Make sure that you have the infrastructure to accommodate the offer and that you have people dedicated to following up with any signups. All follow ups need to be done within 30 minutes from when a lead opts in to your offer. After 30 minutes, your chances to lose the lead increases.
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;a&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/md/unsplash/dms3rep/multi/photo-1525182008055-f88b95ff7980.jpg" alt=""/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;h3 style=""&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         Conclusion
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;span style="background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           Now it is time to get your business on the internet map. For some it is already too late. The only way of surviving this economic recession is to go digital. You have the tools available at your fingertips to make a success of your business. 
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 13:43:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>ockert@comcat.co.za (Ockert Fourie)</author>
      <guid>http://www.comcat.co.za/reboot-your-business</guid>
      <g-custom:tags type="string">reboot business</g-custom:tags>
      <media:content medium="image" url="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/reboot+economy.jpg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Small Businesses Need an Online Presence</title>
      <link>http://www.comcat.co.za/why-small-businesses-need-an-online-presence</link>
      <description />
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 style="transition: opacity 1s ease-in-out 0s;"&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         Online marketing
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/md/unsplash/dms3rep/multi/photo-1556155092-490a1ba16284.jpg"/&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div style="text-align: justify; transition: none 0s ease 0s; display: block;" data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         There are many ways to market a small business to attract customers. You can advertise using signs, newspaper ads, radio or even television. Some of these methods are more affordable than others and with changes in media some are more far reaching than others. A sign is affordable but may only attract local traffic. Television ads may reach many but are expensive and may not provide a return. So, what is an affordable and far reaching way to attract customers? The answer: online marketing.
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;h3&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         Why Use Online Marketing? 
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;span style="background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           People have become more active online than ever before with smart phones placing the internet at their fingertips. This means that if a business is looking for customers, the best place to find them is online. 
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          While being an affordable marketing platform, online marketing also offers businesses the ability to track how much attention their advertising is attracting. It even gives businesses the opportunity to see what both current and potential customers want by allowing them to interact with businesses in a meaningful way (e.g. filling out surveys). Being online means that a company in one part of the world can be seen by someone in another. Simply put, the potential for reaching customers anywhere and anytime is endless. 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Despite all of this, the online environment can be a daunting thing to approach for businesses. There are many places to go, many tools to use and it can sometimes just seem simpler to make your own sign and put it up on the side of the road every time you open and take it down when you close. But most businesses have competitors and most competitors have an online presence. So to be competitive, it only seems fair that a business needs to have an online presence. 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;h3 style=""&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         Go Where Your Customers Are 
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;a&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/md/unsplash/dms3rep/multi/photo-1534532022510-1d839b268414.jpg" alt=""/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          A fisherman does not climb a tree in the middle of the desert to find a deep sea fish. A fisherman goes to the deep sea. Similarly, the online environment is teaming with potential customers ready to see what you have to offer. If you are not there for them to see you, you will miss an opportunity to attract them and they are more likely to go to your competitor instead. 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Having an online presence can also make you appear to be more legitimate and accessible. It also gives past customers the ability to review your service or product and in doing so promotes your business further to potential customers. It also provides feedback for you to enable you to improve your business to achieve more customer satisfaction. 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          If you are online but are not appearing when your clients are searching for the product or service you provide, you are invisible to them and your competitors gain an advantage. So it is important to make sure that you use all of the online tools available to market your company well enough so that it appears when your clients or potential clients search for keywords that relate to your company. 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          As well as this, when your clients find you, you need to be set up online in such a way as to be easily comparable to your clients. This means that they need to be able to navigate your page to discover where you are located, contact details, prices for services and so forth. Discerning clients will compare companies, so, as mentioned below, it is important to know what your competitors are doing. 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;h3 style=""&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         Learn From Your Competitors  
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;span style="background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           Business is a race with multiple runners. If a particular business does not have an online presence, or does not come up when customers search for the service or product the business provides, their competitors have a head start while that business is far behind and carrying extra weight that makes it difficult to even take part in the race. 
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Like athletes, it is important to learn from those you are competing against. What do they do well, what do they do poorly and what would you do differently to do better? They may use various tools such as blogs, videos/vlogs or graphics to attract attention. They may showcase their brand in a certain way to make it different and stand out from the crowd. They may interact with their customers, both current and potential, and capture their attention in a unique and pleasant manner. There are many things competitors do that can be modified to promote a business. It is also important to remember that even if a business has been online for a while, it can still learn from its competitors and what they are doing to keep things interesting for their customers. 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;h3 style=""&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         Is Online Marketing For You? 
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         Based on the above points, it is safe to say that it is.
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 12:55:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>ockert@comcat.co.za (Ockert Fourie)</author>
      <guid>http://www.comcat.co.za/why-small-businesses-need-an-online-presence</guid>
      <g-custom:tags type="string" />
      <media:content medium="image" url="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/md/unsplash/dms3rep/multi/photo-1571204829887-3b8d69e4094d.jpg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beauty Salons - Tatoo Artists and Resturants!!! What do they have in common</title>
      <link>http://www.comcat.co.za/beauty-salons-tatoo-artists-and-resturants-what-do-they-have-in-common</link>
      <description />
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 style="transition: opacity 1s ease-in-out 0s;"&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         These are some of the industries that will be allowed to start opening their doors in Advanced Level 3 Lockdown
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/HD+-+TA+-+R.jpg"/&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div style="transition: none 0s ease 0s; display: block;" data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         The South African Government has decided to allow some of the industries that has close contact to one another to open their doors for the first time since lockdown. 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          The industries affected is:
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;li&gt;&#xD;
        
                        
            Restaurants – allowing for sit-down meals;
           
                      &#xD;
      &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;li&gt;&#xD;
        
                        
            Accredited and licensed accommodation facilities (except Airbnb);
           
                      &#xD;
      &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;li&gt;&#xD;
        
                        
            Conferences and meetings for business purposes (in-line with safety guidelines);
           
                      &#xD;
      &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;li&gt;&#xD;
        
                        
            Cinemas and theaters;
           
                      &#xD;
      &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;li&gt;&#xD;
        
                        
            Casinos;
           
                      &#xD;
      &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;li&gt;&#xD;
        
                        
            Personal care services including hairdressers;
           
                      &#xD;
      &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;li&gt;&#xD;
        
                        
            Non-contact sports including tennis, golf, cricket and others;
           
                      &#xD;
      &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;li&gt;&#xD;
        
                        
            Contact sports – only for training.
           
                      &#xD;
      &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           All these industries will need to put systems in place to protect them as well as their customers to prevent the spread of Covid-19.  But what they also need to think of now is their digital presence. People now have the fear of C-19 and are less likely to go out to risk exposure to this deadly virus. Businesses now forced to use other ways to connect to their client. 
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           Using social media is the way forward. It is the easiest and most effective way of getting your message across straight to their ideal audience. Time-and-time again this has proven to be the best way of advertising. Traditional marketing does not target the people that will be a high quality returning client.
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           Areas that will still remain closed are:
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
        &lt;li&gt;&#xD;
          
                          
             The sale of tobacco products;
            
                        &#xD;
        &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
        &lt;li&gt;&#xD;
          
                          
             Social visits between family members;
            
                        &#xD;
        &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
        &lt;li&gt;&#xD;
          
                          
             The country’s borders for international travel and provincial travel for leisure;
            
                        &#xD;
        &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
        &lt;li&gt;&#xD;
          
                          
             Large parts of the events industry – including nightclubs and concerts, and exhibitions.
            
                        &#xD;
        &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
        &lt;li&gt;&#xD;
          
                          
             Sporting events with spectators;
            
                        &#xD;
        &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
        &lt;li&gt;&#xD;
          
                          
             Gyms.
            
                        &#xD;
        &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           Whether your business is still in lockdown, or it is the first week of freedom, it is not too late to start promoting your business. 
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           Have a look at this
           
                      &#xD;
      &lt;a href="/offer"&gt;&#xD;
        
                        
            offer
           
                      &#xD;
      &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 11:29:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>ockert@comcat.co.za (Ockert Fourie)</author>
      <guid>http://www.comcat.co.za/beauty-salons-tatoo-artists-and-resturants-what-do-they-have-in-common</guid>
      <g-custom:tags type="string" />
      <media:content medium="image" url="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/HD+-+TA+-+R.jpg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Africa - Level 3 Lockdown - What it means to your business</title>
      <link>http://www.comcat.co.za/south-africa-level-3-lockdown-what-it-means-to-your-business</link>
      <description>What destruction covid-19 has caused to the economy and people's lives? How businesses need to change they why they service clients and how to get new clients.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 style="text-align: center; transition: opacity 1s ease-in-out 0s;"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;span style=""&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Covid-19 is here to stay. What are businesses going to do?
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/md/unsplash/dms3rep/multi/photo-1526168637801-e9f490d6bc04.jpg"/&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div style="transition: none 0s ease 0s; display: block;" data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         COVID-19… Yes this has been the word that has caused havoc across the world. Governments has locked down their countries. Citizens had mostly obeyed this for the sake of containing the virus and preparing for the influx of patients to hospitals. But the devastation this virus caused the economy was way worse. Any business that rely on being open every day of the month, to be able to provide an income for their employees, is most likely to close down permanently.  People lost their businesses, jobs and any source of income. They are now starving.
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           Across the world, people are now rising up against their governments. The hunger is now overwhelming the fear of COVID-19. In the US, people has started rioting and looting. South Africa has seen a few instances where people has looted shops. Riots broke out because of food shortages. This is going to get worse before we can start to rebuild.
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           Business owners and entrepreneurs must now change the way they operate. They need to put new measures in place to accommodate and protect their clients. The aim is to keep revenues up, while getting expenses as low as possible to be able to pay salaries to their employees.
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           The way to help accomplish this is to change marketing strategy to reach their best potential client at the lowest cost. To accomplish this is to start looking at the internet and social media.
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           South Africa is now going to Level 3 lockdown on 1 July 2020. What does that mean to your business? Unless you are a retailer that provide food and other necessities, people are less likely to come to your business to buy from you. Most people has been affected by this financially in some way to the other. By taking your business or services online?
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           How do you do that? By setting up an e-commerce site to help you promote and sell your products and services to the public. The site needs to be search engine optimizes (SEO) to improve your rankings on search engines. It needs to be responsive on all devices (pc, tablet and mobile). More than 61% of internet use worldwide, is on mobile devices. Your site needs to look modern and perform on any mobile device.  
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           If you only service a specific area, you can do targeted marketing to you ideal client in that area. Your company then saves money and resources while increasing revenue.
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           What sets you apart from your competitors?
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           Many companies has seen the benefit of using the internet and social media. They have already started the migration to the digital world of e-commerce. If you don’t start using the internet to help promote your business, your competitors most probably will. This will give them a great advantage above your company. Help flatten the curve of the unemployment rate and go digital.
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 08:53:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>ockert@comcat.co.za (Ockert Fourie)</author>
      <guid>http://www.comcat.co.za/south-africa-level-3-lockdown-what-it-means-to-your-business</guid>
      <g-custom:tags type="string">godigital,getnewclients,onlinebusiness</g-custom:tags>
      <media:content medium="image" url="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/md/unsplash/dms3rep/multi/photo-1526168637801-e9f490d6bc04.jpg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Need a website?</title>
      <link>http://www.comcat.co.za/need-a-website</link>
      <description />
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 style="transition: opacity 1s ease-in-out 0s;"&gt;&#xD;
  
         Our promo video
        &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div style="transition: none 0s ease 0s; display: block;" data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  
         Created a video... Have a look
        &#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 12:49:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.comcat.co.za/need-a-website</guid>
      <g-custom:tags type="string" />
      <media:content medium="image" url="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/md/unsplash/dms3rep/multi/photo-1454486837617-ce8e1ba5ebfe.jpg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helping Business Survive Covid-19</title>
      <link>http://www.comcat.co.za/helping-business-survive-covid-19</link>
      <description />
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 style="transition: opacity 1s ease-in-out 0s;"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;span style=""&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          FREE Digital Marketing with purchase of any of our websites
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/1+Month%281%29.png"/&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div style="transition: none 0s ease 0s; display: block;" data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;span style="background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
           Covid-19 has dealt a mighty blow to small-to-medium businesses of which some companies will not survive. Not even with the government's bailout.
          
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          We have decided to help companies get on their feet by providing 1 Month FREE Digital marketing service (client pay for ad-spent) with purchase of any of our website. 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          We do have payment plans available. 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Businesses are more than welcome to contact us, even just to chat about strategy. 
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Please schedule a meeting here.
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 20:43:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.comcat.co.za/helping-business-survive-covid-19</guid>
      <g-custom:tags type="string" />
      <media:content medium="image" url="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/1+Month%281%29.png" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to salvage my business while in country is in ‘lockdown’?</title>
      <link>http://www.comcat.co.za/how-to-salvage-my-business-while-in-country-is-in-lockdown</link>
      <description />
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 style="transition: opacity 1s ease-in-out 0s;"&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
         South Africa moving to level 4 lockdown
        
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                
                &#xD;
&lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/md/unsplash/dms3rep/multi/photo-1584931423298-c576fda54bd2.jpg"/&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div style="transition: none 0s ease 0s; display: block;" data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;b style="text-decoration-line: underline;"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
           Where it all started for us?
          
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
         When the first case of the covid-19 virus (aka corona) was reported, in December 2019, little did we know what impact this will make to the world as we know it. This microbe has now traveled the world and has infected people across all countries. Like many other South Africans, this is the first time that I experience a ‘lockdown’ of a country. This has never happened in my lifetime on this scale. What this ‘lockdown’ has done is put everything into perspective. Life will go on. This gives us now time to prepare for when the ‘lockdown’ is lifted and the curve has been flatten. 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  &#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;span style="text-decoration-line: underline;"&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;b&gt;&#xD;
        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
                        
            The downside of the virus
           
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      &#xD;
      &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;/span&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
          Except for the loss of life and the thousands of people being placed into quarantine, it has disrupted our day to day activities. Our economy is going to take a lot of strain as well as businesses that are forced to close down. If you are running a business that provide non-essential services and products, then this could be you. 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;b style="text-decoration-line: underline;"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
           What to do next?
          
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
          Use this lockdown period to plan your next move. Put systems in to place that will work for you while you are unable to. You are still able to contact people using phone, email, skype, whatapp and zoom. Use these platforms at your disposal to get the ball rolling. My preference is zoom, because you have the ability to do share screen and presentations. Hosting a one-on-one on free package is has no time limitations, but doing a webinar to many is limited to 40min. This is still sufficient to get your message across. It is time to clean up the cobwebs from your old/outdated site and spruce it up. Having a responsive design and also optimized for proper click through rate is key. This will also help to boost your search engine optimization (SEO) rankings. Another option is to have some type of promotion and using social media platforms to target the people that is most likely to use your products and services. It is now time to take massive action. This will determine if your company is going to be prosperous or struggling. 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;b style="text-decoration-line: underline;"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
           How can we help you?
          
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
          We will be available in the lockdown to help businesses get ready for after ‘lockdown’. We will guide you step-by-step from marketing strategy to having a proper website that is optimized for all devices (pc, tablet and mobile). 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
          Our team is waiting on you.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
          E-mail:
          
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    &#xD;
    &lt;a href="mailto:info@comcat.co.za"&gt;&#xD;
      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
                      
           info@comcat.co.za
          
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    &#xD;
    &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    
          Be safe, stay indoors and all the best.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 17:55:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.comcat.co.za/how-to-salvage-my-business-while-in-country-is-in-lockdown</guid>
      <g-custom:tags type="string" />
      <media:content medium="image" url="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/md/unsplash/dms3rep/multi/photo-1584931423298-c576fda54bd2.jpg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Reasons Why You Need a Digital Media Strategy</title>
      <link>http://www.comcat.co.za/6-reasons-why-you-need-a-digital-media-strategy</link>
      <description />
      <content:encoded>&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/BLOGPOST_1-1920x1280.jpg"/&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div style="transition: none 0s ease 0s; display: block;" data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         Everyone needs a digital media strategy, and not for the reasons you may expect. In fact, if you think digital strategies are just promotional, think again.
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 14:51:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>rudy@optimizedgroup.io (Rudy Bekker)</author>
      <guid>http://www.comcat.co.za/6-reasons-why-you-need-a-digital-media-strategy</guid>
      <g-custom:tags type="string" />
      <media:content medium="image" url="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/BLOGPOST_1-1920x1280.jpg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#1 Most Important Part of Your Campaign</title>
      <link>http://www.comcat.co.za/1-most-important-part-of-your-campaign</link>
      <description />
      <content:encoded>&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/BLOGPOST_4-1920x1280.jpg"/&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div style="transition: none 0s ease 0s; display: block;" data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         If you think money is the only thing that matters in your campaign, think again. There are many more things to think about.
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 14:50:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.comcat.co.za/1-most-important-part-of-your-campaign</guid>
      <g-custom:tags type="string" />
      <media:content medium="image" url="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/BLOGPOST_4-1920x1280.jpg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes from the Other Side</title>
      <link>http://www.comcat.co.za/notes-from-the-other-side</link>
      <description />
      <content:encoded>&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/BLOGPOST_2-890x593.jpg"/&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div style="transition: none 0s ease 0s; display: block;" data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         Always wondered what happens on the other side of your campaign. Well, now you’re going to find out.
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 14:49:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>rudy@optimizedgroup.io (Rudy Bekker)</author>
      <guid>http://www.comcat.co.za/notes-from-the-other-side</guid>
      <g-custom:tags type="string" />
      <media:content medium="image" url="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/BLOGPOST_2-890x593.jpg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Technology isn't Enough for Your Digital Campaign</title>
      <link>http://www.comcat.co.za/why-technology-isn-t-enough-for-your-digital-campaign</link>
      <description />
      <content:encoded>&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/BLOGPOST_5-890x594.jpg"/&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div style="transition: none 0s ease 0s; display: block;" data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  
                  
         Just because you have a snazzy Facebook, Instagram and Snapchat campaign doesn’t mean you’re covered.
        
                &#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 14:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>rudy@optimizedgroup.io (Rudy Bekker)</author>
      <guid>http://www.comcat.co.za/why-technology-isn-t-enough-for-your-digital-campaign</guid>
      <g-custom:tags type="string" />
      <media:content medium="image" url="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/BLOGPOST_5-890x594.jpg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 4 Questions About Instagram - Answered</title>
      <link>http://www.comcat.co.za/top-4-questions-about-instagram</link>
      <description />
      <content:encoded>&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;a&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;img src="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/BLOGPOST_3-1920x1280.jpg" alt="" title=""/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div style="text-align:left;" data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;p style=""&gt;&#xD;
    
                    
          Wondering who’s following whom, who you should follow, and what follows what’s being followed? We’re here to explain.
         
                  &#xD;
  &lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 14:43:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>rudy@optimizedgroup.io (Rudy Bekker)</author>
      <guid>http://www.comcat.co.za/top-4-questions-about-instagram</guid>
      <g-custom:tags type="string" />
      <media:content medium="image" url="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/BLOGPOST_3-1920x1280.jpg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Reasons You Should Love Blogging</title>
      <link>http://www.comcat.co.za/10-reasons-you-should-love-blogging</link>
      <description />
      <content:encoded>&lt;div data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;h3&gt;&#xD;
    
          Blog posts are a great way to get recognized within your community and share your voice. Here are the top 10 reasons you should love writing blog posts.
         &#xD;
  &lt;/h3&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;a&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;img src="//dd-cdn.multiscreensite.com/blog/blog_post_image_2.jpeg" alt="" title=""/&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;div style="text-align:left;" data-rss-type="text"&gt;&#xD;
  &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;b&gt;&#xD;
      
           Anyone can make one:
          &#xD;
    &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    
          For better or worse, anyone can write a blog post about anything they want. Everyone has a voice and thet voices will rise to the top.
          &#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;b&gt;&#xD;
      
           The writer can show their personality:
          &#xD;
    &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    
          In blog posts, the writer has more leeway to add in their voice and personality than other types of writing.
          &#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;b&gt;&#xD;
      
           Blogs are a great form of mass communication:
          &#xD;
    &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    
          You can help people, learn new things, entertain your audience-the possibilities are endless and amazing. Blogging opens up all of these to a very wide audience.
          &#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;b&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
      
           You can make money:
          &#xD;
    &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    
          Get the right blog going and you can make a lot of money through advertising and sponsored posts.
          &#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;b&gt;&#xD;
      
           It allows people to craft better thoughts:
          &#xD;
    &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    
          Instead of reading haphazard, uneducated Facebook statuses, it's much better to see people's thought process in a well-written blog post.
          &#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;b&gt;&#xD;
      
           You can establish a community:
          &#xD;
    &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    
          Blogging allows you to connect with other individuals who share the same interests. Sharing ideas and opinions within your community helps establish yourself as a thought leader.
          &#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;b&gt;&#xD;
      
           Good for SEO:
          &#xD;
    &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    
          Keeping content on your site fresh and relevant, you can use your blog to boost the search engine ranking (SEO) of your site and your business.
          &#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;b&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
      
           It brings people back to your site:
          &#xD;
    &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    
          If your blog is strong enough and updated regularly, people will come back looking for more and bring traffic back to your site as well.
          &#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;b&gt;&#xD;
      
           It's free:
          &#xD;
    &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    
          It costs you a grand total of zero dollars to post to the blog, so if you have something to say, there's nothing to stop you.
          &#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;b&gt;&#xD;
      &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
      
           You can establish yourself as a thought leader:
          &#xD;
    &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    
          A blog is a great place for your original thoughts, and it can be a wonderful way to show off your individuality. If people like your ideas, you can become a thought leader in your industry!
          &#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;
    
          What else do you love about blogs? Let me know!
         &#xD;
  &lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 14:43:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>rudy@optimizedgroup.io (Rudy Bekker)</author>
      <guid>http://www.comcat.co.za/10-reasons-you-should-love-blogging</guid>
      <g-custom:tags type="string" />
      <media:content medium="image" url="https://irp-cdn.multiscreensite.com/01df3044/dms3rep/multi/BLOGPOST_6-1920x1440.jpg" />
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
